Guide to the Vassar College Subject Files, 1864–2023
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- V. C. Vassar College Film Society, see: V. C. Film Club
- V. C. Vassar College Legal Society (Folder 25.59)
- V. C. Vassar Committee on Famine Relief, see: V. C. Famine Relief Committee
- V. C. Vassar Cookbook (Folder 25.60)
- V. C. Vassar Cooperative Bookstore (Folder 25.61)
- V. C. Vassar Daily, see: Vassariana in Process
- V. C. Vassar Dance Group (Folder 25.62)
- V. C. Vassar Dance Theatre (Folder 25.63)
- V. C. Vassar Dramatic Workshop (Folder 25.64)
- V. C. Vassar Drive (Folder 25.65)
- V. C. Vassar Emergency Fund (Folder 25.66)
- V. C. Vassar Environmental Society/Group (Folder 25.67)
- V. C. Vassar Exchange, see: V. C. Furniture Exchange
- V. C. Vassar Film Workshop (Folder 25.68)
- V. C. Vassar "Firsts" (Folder 25.69)
- V. C. Vassar Inquiry (club) (Folder 25.70)
- V. C. Vassar International Students Association (Folder 25.71)
- V. C. Vassar Investment Research Committee (Folder 25.72)
- V. C. Vassar Jewish Student Union (Folder 25.73)
- V. C. Vassar Jewish Student Union; The Spirit (newsletter) (Folder 25.74)
- V. C. Vassar Legal Society (Folder 25.75)
- V. C. Vassar Missionary Society (Folder 25.76)
- V. C. Vassar Mugs, see: V. C. China and Silver
- V. C. Vassar Players (Folder 25.77)
- V. C. Vassar Progressive Union, see also: V. C. Coalition for Social Responsibility (Folder 25.78)
- V. C. Vassar Scholars' Lectures (Folder 25.79)
- V. C. Vassar Students' Aid Society (Folder 25.80)
- V. C. Vassar Students Association, 1979- (Folder 25.81)
- V. C. Vassar Summer Institute (Announcements) (Folder 25.82)
- V. C. Vassar Summer Institute (General) (Folder 25.83)
- V. C. Vassar Summer Institute (folder for each year), 1925-1958 (Folder 25.84-26.32)
- V. C. Vassar Swimming Club (Folder 26.33)
- V. C. Vassar-Yale Study, see: Yale-Vassar Study
- V. C. Vassar Zionist Alliance (Folder 26.34)
- V. C. Verse (Folder 26.35)
- V. C. Veterans (General) (Folder 26.36)
- V. C. Veterans. Biography (Folder 26.37)
- V. C. Veterans. Clippings (Folder 26.38)
- V. C. Veterans. Committee Reports and Minutes (RESTRICTED) (Folder 26.39)
- V. C. Veterans. Committee Reports and Minutes (Folder 26.39a)
- V. C. Veterans. Correspondence - about (RESTRICTED) (Folder 25.40)
- V. C. Veterans. Correspondence - with (Folder 26.41)
- V. C. Veterans. Records (RESTRICTED) (Folder 26.42)
- V. C. Veterans' Association (Folder 26.43)
- V. C. Vice-President for Administration (Folder 26.44)
- V. C. Vice-President for Student Affairs (Folder 26.45)
- V. C. Vietnam Moratorium, etc. (Folder 26.46-26.47)
- V. C. Visiting Resident Lecture Series, 1977- (Folder 26.48)
- V. C. Visitors (Folder 26.49)
- V. C. Vocational Bureau, see also: V. C. Career Planning and Placement, Office of (Folder 26.50)
- V. C. Vocational Bureau. Conferences (Folder 26.51)
- V. C. Vocational Bureau. Reports on classes after graduation (Folder 26.52-26.53)
- V. C. Vocational Bureau. Reports on summer activities (Folder 26.54)
- V. C. Vocational Training (Folder 26.55)
- V. C. Wake Robin Club (Folder 26.56)
- V. C. War Activities, 1917-1918 (Folder 26.57-26.60)
- V. C. War Activities, 1941-1945 (Folder 26.61)
- V. C. Warden (Folder 26.62)
- V. C. Warden. Annual Reports (Folder 26.63)
- V. C. Washington's Birthday Celebrations (Folder 26.64)
- V. C. Wendy R. Breslau Award, 1971- (Folder 27.1)
- V. C. William Borden Fund (Folder 27.2)
- V. C. William K. Rose Fellowships in the Creative Arts (Folder 27.3)
- V. C. William White Forrester and Hugh White Memorial Lecture (Folder 27.4)
- V. C. Wind Ensemble, 1982- (Folder 27.5)
- V. C. Wing Farm, see: V. C. Campus
- V. C. Winter Weekend (Folder 27.6)
- V. C. Women's Center (Folder 27.7)
- V. C. Women's Exercise Group (Folder 27.8)
- V. C. Women's Liberation (Folder 27.9)
- V. C. Woodworking and Ceramics Shop, see V. C. Craft Shop
- V. C. Woodrow Wilson Centennial (Folder 27.10)
- V. C. Workshop Bureau of Plays (Folder 27.11)
- V. C. World Citizenship Club (Folder 27.12)
- V. C. Year-round Operation (Folder 27.13)
- V. C. Young Democrats Club, see: Vassar Democratic Club
- V. C. Young Republican Club, see: Vassar Young Republican Club
- V. C. Young Women's Christian Association (Folder 27.14)
- Vassar Committee for Civil Rights, see: V. C. Vassar Civil Rights Committee
- Vassar Cooperative Bookshop (Folder 27.15-27.16)
- Vassar Cooperative Bookshop. History (Folder 27.17)
- Vassar Daily Newsletter, see also: V. C. Vassar Daily, 1968- (Folder 27.18)
- Vassar Democratic Club (Folder 27.19)
- Vassar Doll (Folder 27.20)
- Vassar Emergency Relief Drive (Folder 27.21)
- Vassar Families (several generation of Vassar Students), see: V. C. Granddaughters...
- Vassar Film Guild (Folder 27.22)
- Vassar Film Workshop, see: V. C. Vassar Film Workshop
- Vassar "Firsts", see: V. C. Vassar 'Firsts"
- "Vassar Follies" (Folder 27.23)
- Vassar Food Co-op, see: V. C. Food Co-operatives
- Vassar Glacier (Folder 27.24)
- Vassar in a Nutshell (Folder 27.25)
- Vassar in China (Folder 27.26)
- Vassar in Japan (Folder 27.27)
- Vassar Institute for Women in Business (Folder 27.28)
- Vassar Journal of Undergraduate Studies (Folder 27.29)
- Vassar Medieval Studies (Folder 27.30)
- Vassar Millay Society, see: V. C. Millay Society
- Vassar Miscellany (Folder 27.31)
- Vassar Miscellany News (Folder 27.32)
- Vassar Planet (Folder 27.33)
- Vassar Players (Folder 27.34)
- Vassar Printing Club (Folder 27.35)
- Vassar Progressive Citizens of America, see: V. C. Progressive Citizens of America
- Vassar Quarterly, see also: Vassar Alumnae Magazine (Folder 27.36)
- Vassar Review (Folder 27.37)
- Vassar (High School) Senior Seminar (Folder 27.38)
- Vassar Spectator (Folder 27.39)
- Vassar Students Association-Newsletter (Folder 27.40)
- Vassar Vagabond (Folder 27.41)
- Vassar-Wellesley Summer Internship Program (Washington, D.C.) (Folder 27.42)
- Vassar-Wellesley Program (Semester in Spain), 1969- (Folder 27.43)
- Vassar-Yale Study, see also: V. C. New Dimensions Committee on, 1967 (Folder 27.44-27.47)
- Vassar Young Republican Club (Folder 27.48)
- Vassarion (Folder 27.49)
- Vassarion (Illustrations) (Folder 27.50)
- "Vassar's Folly", see: The V.C. Drama Department Collection, a separate collection which includes photographs, programs, flyers, and other materials related to the organization and this production
- Wagner Inn (Folder 27.51)
- Walt Foundation (Folder 27.52)
- War Chest of Greater Poughkeepsie (Folder 27.53)
- Welcome Alternative, see: V. C. Food Co-operatives
- Wellesley-Vassar Summer Internship Programs, see: Vassar-Wellesley Summer Internship Program
- Womanspeak (Folder 27.54)
- Women's City and County Club, 1919-1968 (Folder 27.55)
- Women's College Board (Folder 27.56)
- Women's Intercollegiate Association for Student Government (Folder 27.57)
- Workshop in Computer Mathematics (Folder 27.58)
- World Youth Congress, Second, 1938 (Folder 27.59-27.61)
- Yelping Hill, Connecticut (MacCracken Home, also Ruth Adams '04), see: MacCracken Papers
- Die Zeitung German Newsletter (Folder 27.62)